rici4you.com 2016-10-25

# RICI-EN Privacy Policy | Royal Innovation Club International

We recognizes the importance of protecting your privacy and our policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site. This policy will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers' needs.

You must comply with the Terms and Conditions of use of products, services and information provided to you by us. In our Terms and Conditions it is expressly stated that, should you make legible in any way the access information to your account even by choosing a password that may be easily linked to your personal details you will have abused the service and will not receive any compensation for loss or damage to your property. You must choose a password that cannot be guessed, change your password every 6 months, always have an anti-virus software, do not send personal information to anyone even us. Remember to log out of the website before you leave your computer, by being in a contract with us you agree the responsibility of strict confidentiality of all personal information in relation to our contract.

##### WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

When you visit this website you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and website use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Website.

The information you provide will be held for as long as you have an account with us after which to be removed from our database you must inform us, we are legally obliged to hold such information for a minimum of 6 years.

##### PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU CHOOSE TO PROVIDE

Any changes in personal information will also be stored and a note of the change will be recorded. The information we obtain is but not limited to: name, address, date of birth, email address, contact number(s), website usage, preferences & interests, credit & financial history, county court judgements, bankruptcies, browser usage, operating system, IP address, Internet Service Provider, user demographic information, statistical information about your use of our services. The information may be disclosed to regulators, lawyers, auditors, court judgements, anti-money laundering and fraud prevention agencies. All information provided will be transferable assets in the case of our takeover.

Email Information: If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.  
Website Use Information: Similar to other commercial websites, our Website utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" and webserver log files to collect information about how our Website is used. Information gathered through cookies and webserver logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Website, and the websites visited just before and just after our Website.

##### HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE TO US?

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing the products and services you requested, to process your payment, to monitor the use of the service, our marketing and promotional efforts and improve our content and service offerings, and customize our site's content, layout, services and for other lawful purposes. These uses improve our site and better tailor it to meet your needs.   
Furthermore, such information may be shared with others on an aggregate basis. Personally identifiable information or business information will not be shared with parties except as required by law.

Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Website, new services, and special offers we think you will find valuable.  
We also share your information with the individual who referred you to this site. They may use that information to contact you directly. In the event you wish to discontinue receiving information from us you can simply engage the auto removal feature available at the bottom of EVERY email we send to you. Should your sponsor contact you outside our system you must inform them, individually, of your desire to be removed from their mailing list. Otherwise, your information is NOT shared with anyone else.

##### HOW DO WE USE INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM COOKIES?

As you visit and browse our Website, the site uses cookies to differentiate you from other users. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you from having to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our Webserver's log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our Website and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback to constantly improve our Website and better serve our clients. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not intentionally store any personal information that your browser provided to us in your cookies.

##### IP ADDRESSES

IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as traffic data so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you.

##### SHARING AND SELLING INFORMATION

We do not share, sell, lend or lease any of the information that uniquely identify a subscriber (such as email addresses or personal details) with anyone except to the extent it is necessary to process transactions or provide services that you have requested.

##### HOW CAN YOU ACCESS AND CORRECT YOUR INFORMATION?

You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by emailing us at the usual address.  

##### WHAT ABOUT LEGALLY COMPELLED DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION?

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights. We may also disclose account information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms of Service or to protect the safety of our users and the Public.

To prevent fraud your information may be used to monitor potentially illegal transactions. If you wish to inform us at any stage of your contract that you do not wish your information to be used other than for the purpose of the contract then we will not disclose your information except to crime and fraud prevention agencies with authority.

Credit rating agencies may require your information to assess the risk of providing credit; this is not a credit check and your information will not be provided if expressly stated in writing.

##### WHAT ABOUT OTHER WEBSITES LINKED TO OUR WEBSITE?

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Website or the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Website. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Website to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites, which have a link on our Website, is subject to that website's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

##### YOUR CONSENT

By using our Website you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice.

##### OUR COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY:

Please note that your information will be stored and processed on our computers in the United States. The laws on holding personal data in the United States may be less stringent than the laws of your Country of residence or citizenship. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

You must never provide information by those posing as us; remember that we will never contact you requesting information such as your date of birth or account access details. It is imperative that you forward such requests to us at [support@rici4you.com](mailto:support@rici4you.com) as soon as you can. For your protection we will automatically lock an attempt to access your account if 3 failed attempts occur, in order to have this lock removed you must contact us verifying personal information before being granted access.

##### ACQUISITION OR CHANGES IN OWNERSHIP

In the event that the website (or a substantial portion of its assets) is acquired, your information would be considered part of those assets, and may be part of those assets that are transferred.

##### POLICY MODIFICATIONS

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent.
